Hary:
Hallo?
Is it in?
Nia:
Yes, it is
Hary:
The voice? Okay
Shall we start?
Hary:
Assalamu'alaikum Warahmatullahi Wabarakatuh
Nia & Atikah:
Wa'alaikumsalam Warahmatullahi Wabarakatuh
Hary:
Alhamdulillah
Right now, we can meet here and we already decided before
Hary:
What application we use to review the UI and UX,
that we will make for the improvisation
Hary:
There is application called “Tell”
It's like, you guys already knew
Hary:
This application is kind of like any other social media.
Kinda like Wattpad, mixed with Facebook
Hary:
So it can send comment and make stories
There something special about it, that the sender is anonymous
Hary:
You guys already try it before right?
And we already agreed to search
Hary:
The thing we must improve form this app
either from the UI or UX
Hary:
So from that, what do you think Atikah?
Atikah:
For login page
Google icon is to small
Atikah:
And the table for tick isn’t easy to see
So
Atikah:
The user might get confused
User don’t know
Atikah:
if they should click the tick
or google icon first
Atikah:
Then, google icon better placed in the center
Because, if it's placed at the bottom it isn’t easy to see.
There is also, setting page
Atikah:
This, there is
There is sign out button
Atikah:
It’s better to place it at the bottom
Hary:
Why though?
Atikah:
Attribution, after attribution
Hary:
Yes, why?
Atikah:
If it’s placed there
User might accidentally press the sign out button
Hary:
That right, they put it above and bellow fingerprint
Atikah:
Yes, it should be at the bottom
Let it be sequential
Nia:
it's weird
Hary:
Yes, that right
Nia:
Yes, also
If you pay attention, it's like the layout get cut off
it's long right? but it's like get cut off and there is fingerprint
Nia:
at the middle
Hary:
Yes, it's a bit confusing
Nia:
The placement
Atikah:
Yes it's confusing
Hary:
And then, what else Tik?
Atikah:
And then, there is Tellizen Community
There tell on twitter, tell on instagram,
tell on medium, tell on discord, it should be
Atikah:
It better if didn't  write tell on there
so that
Atikah:
So that, there no waste of words
Hary:
Yes, so there no repeated words
Nia:
Yes, that's right
Atikah:
Yes ry
Nia:
Isn't it the same?
There words 'tell on' but there also icon
isn't it just the same?
Atikah:
Yes, it's better just the icon
Hary:
Yes, that's right
Just the icon
People even know that icon twitter
Nia:
Yes
Just the icon
so it will be short
Atikah:
Yes, there no need for the words
Nia:
It's wasting and
To covering the emptiness
I don't know, it better not be
Hary:
Anything else, Tik?
Nia:
Come on, Tik
Atikah:
Also, column user interface exchange with
tellizen communtiy
Hary:
Why exchange?
Atikah:
So user easy to find it
What?
Hary:
Exchange? Why?
Atikah:
It's easier for user
if they want dark mode or not
so they don't have to scroll down
Hary:
Yes, so like sequentially right?
Nia:
Yes
Atikah:
so it's sequentially and neat
Nia:
But that's right
usually if you see other application
Nia:
Like, if you want to send to other app
they usually put it at the bottom
Nia:
Usually
Atikah:
Yes, usually like that
Hary:
Usually like that, right?
Something like community or another social media
Hary:
at the bottom
also user interface at the bottom
like
Hary:
How?
Just weird isn't?
Nia:
This is just, a bit confusing
why they put it like that
I didn't understand
Nia:
I really didn't understand
Hary:
Anything else Tik?
Nia:
Anything else?
Atikah:
I think enough
Nia:
Enough?
Atikah:
Enough
Hary:
Oke, thank you Tik
Atikah done, now
Atikah:
You're welcome
Hary:
So, Nia
How it is, Nia?
Nia:
As for me
it is in Home page
Nia:
Home page
Hary:
Oke home page
Atikah:
Yes, home page
Nia:
So in the home page
It is quite a lot
Nia:
First, the button
There home button, I already tried it
Hary:
Where?
Nia:
There home
Hary:
Where the button?
Nia:
Can you point it out?
Hary:
The one shape like house?
Atikah:
This one Ni?
Nia:
The one shape like a house, yes
That one, this is a home page
why is there a home button
Nia:
There no, what it's called?
there no function
that's what I meant
Nia:
Why put home button at home page
that the first one
Hary:
Now that you mention it
Nia:
Right?
That's weird right?
Atikah:
That's right
Nia:
Home page
But there a home button
home button like that usually at
Nia:
Like in fun corner, if you want back to home
there home button right?
Nia:
But there isn't, what I meant is
Why put it at home page?
When that actually home, right?
Nia:
Then, on 'Hi Tellizen' sentences
Also the card of fun corner and stories
Nia:
I think it's a little down
That's
Atikah:
That's right
Nia:
Above it
Kinda empty
Atikah:
Like just empty?
Nia:
The way they put it
How do I say it, like
Nia:
What is it again?
Kinda, not good to look at
after all it's just empty
but
Hary:
Too much space right?
Nia:
The space is unreasonable
Also the picture they use as wallpaper page (background)
Nia:
The 2 persons in the picture
isn't it a bit too long?
Nia:
Look at below
Either it's just adjusting to the picture size
I don't know
Nia:
And then, for the notification button
The placement is a bit
Nia:
On the right corner
I think it isn't suit
Nia:
So usually notification is
Even though, there is some who put it there
but not just notification
Nia:
But there also more
Hary:
So there another one like that?
Atikah:
Yes, there another one
Nia:
But this is just notification
Hary:
It's separated
Nia:
It's a bit kinda
It's separated with the one below
why not just put it together
Nia:
You know like
Can I say the brand?
Hary & Atikah:
It's okay
Nia:
Say the brand?
Like shopee
Nia:
For shopee, notification and others is the same on the bottom
It's just like, nice to have all application or features
all of it at the bottom so
Nia:
It's nice so we can just search it at one place
Atikah:
Yes, It's easier
Nia:
It's made more easier to search
And also the icon is just a line
that's meant
Nia:
It's hard to see with background like this
Isn't?
Hary & Atikah:
Yes, it's hard to see it
Nia:
Before that, you can't see it right?
Hary:
I can't see it
Nia:
You can't see it right?
Before, I got a notification from my phone
Nia:
I also open, what the name?
I also open the application
That when I see the notifaction, you know from the phone
the slide one
Nia:
There is notification, but
from the app I can't see it
Nia:
I got confused
The notification icon isn't visible, yes
Hary:
It's just line after all?
Nia:
Yes, it's just line
and I can't see it with the background like that
so like that
Nia:
So isn't right, I think it's better to place it at the bottom
Together with another features
like for chatting and setting
Nia:
And then
Hary:
What else Ni?
Atikah:
Nia:
I think that's all...
Oh, and the color choice isn't that good
Hary:
Which color?
Nia:
In general?
It's kinda a bit
The color choice is
Nia:
Like
It's nice to see it
but isn't it just white?
Nia:
Just white, I meant the background is just white
Hary:
Lack variation?
Atikah:
Yes
Nia:
Just white, the background is just white
but
Nia:
Kinda like not really
Hary:
Like monotone?
Nia:
Yes, monotone and
The function?
like there is person chat just that right?
It's like
Nia:
What is this?
What that person doing?
What kind of application is this?
Actually it's kind of confusing
Nia:
What to do?
Atikah:
Oh, it's lack directions?
Nia:
It lack directions, that's for sure
just from the looks
Nia:
Also adding from before, there a lot of space
that's meant
Nia:
Lack adding information and others
For the application
Hary:
If we want a lot
if they want to empty it
It should be added by something
Nia:
Yes, added something
Atikah:
Yes
Hary:
It wouldn't be that empty
Nia:
Yes, like that
Hary:
Actually
Anything else Ni?
Nia:
Maybe, that's all
Maybe I will add it later
Hary:
Now, from me
Nia:
Maybe, Hary
Hary:
If it's from me, this is from stories and fun corner
Now, we go to stories first
Hary:
This is, added a bit from what Nia said
Connected with home page
Hary:
This is, if we see it
At the bottom navigation bar
there is stories, my profile, and bookmark
right?
Hary:
It's different with
Atikah:
Yes
Hary:
Bottom bar navigation, bottom navigation bar
At home, get back to home
Nia:
The one before right?
Hary:
It's kind of different
If we click stories, and in to
get in to the stories Tik
Atikah:
This one right?
Hary:
Yes, it's look kinda different
Now, try to the fun corner page Tik
Atikah:
This?
Hary:
No, no, fun corner more
The one
this one, this is fun corner
Hary:
It's look like, there no bottom navigation bar
So there features fun corner and stories
it's should be the same, there should be both
a bottom navigation bar, but there none
Hary:
And there 3 dots above
inside it is my post and bookmark
Hary:
Different from stories, where the my post and bookmark
placed at the bottom
Hary:
In bottom navigation bar, so
Atikah:
Yes, there it is
Hary:
Like this, yes
it's kinda like
Hary:
What is it? Kinda unstable
features one and another
Hary:
I suggest
Nia:
It's not consistent
Hary:
For the home page, yes
for the home page, let's back to home page
Hary:
For the home page, it's better we didn't use this
we use the home page
Hary:
The one in stories, but the home page button
is for universal. For all features, wherever we want
it still there
Hary:
The bottom navigation bar, same like Facebook
In facebook there one at above all, always there
Atikah:
Yes
Hary:
But this one is at the bottom
Nia:
Yes there is
Hary:
So if we want
We want to click any features
it always there, we back again
Hary:
To the 3 features
There also features home
Nia:
Yes
Hary:
The home one, Nia said it can't right?
Nia:
Yes it can't
Hary:
It can't get clicked?
Nia:
Yes it can't, it's confusing
Hary:
It's would be better if we make the home as
it should be
Hary:
So, in home there like this
fun corner and stories, later beside it
if we click anything it would change to
can we see the stories one Tik?
Nia:
This one?
Atikah:
This
Hary:
So, for this navigation the one in the stories
we made as navigation for home page, the main one
so, the stories one we change it to be the home page
there my profile and stories, we change it to home page
Hary:
Inside home page is the features to stories and fun corner
In fun corner, there 3 dots above
it's not easy to see it
Nia:
Yes
Hary:
The purpose
Atikah:
This one
Hary:
The purpose is for
That one, the one above
Hary:
if we click we can see bookmark
We can see bookmark from fun corner and post that we post
from fun corner, it's the same features with the one in stories
Hary:
So, it's better if we at the my profile
let's go to my profile
Atikah:
This?
Nia:
Just now
Hary:
Before that
Atikah:
This?
Hary:
No
Nia:
My profile Tik
Hary:
In this my profile, there will be your stories and your post
Post meant that our profile is fun corner
Hary:
So in my profile there is all features, the 2 features
It's also the same for bookmark,
bookmark from stories and fun corner
Hary:
And there also, as you can see there 'Hi Tellizen'
There stories and editor pick
that also I don't understand, what the purpose is
Hary:
It can't get clicked
Atikah:
Yes, it can't get clicked
Nia:
it's the same
Same, I can't understand if it can't get clicked
Hary:
Yes, I can't understand what the purpose
I think that's all
Oh and in the fun corner Tik
Atikah:
This
Hary:
In this fun corner
There 5 elements? 5 category right?
Hary:
There lounge
Atikah & Nia:
Yes
Hary:
There education, beauty, games, and arts
This is as you can see the position
Hary:
Arts not in the center
It's unbalanced
Nia:
Yes
Atikah:
Hary:
So
A bit left, so the fun corner is a bit to center
Hary:
Also, at the post of fun corner
go there Tik
Atikah:
This?
Hary:
Yes, this is
This one
Hary:
There is our post
(reading out one of the post)
there a features
Hary:
For reply, features for like, and 3 dots for other features
And below there a plus to adding a post
it's kinda crash (pile up)
Atikah:
Crash with other icons?
Hary:
Yes, crash with other icons
Kinda pile up
Atikah:
That's right
Hary:
It's better to put it
Atikah:
The right side?
Hary:
So, maybe
Yes, the right side
Atikah:
Right
Hary:
Right? Maybe left?
Nia:
Right?
Atikah:
That's right, the left side
Hary:
That right side
Nia:
Actually it can be both
It can be both betwen reply and post
that meant
Nia:
3 dots on the left or otherwise
Hary:
That's right
Nia:
As long they're not the same
Hary:
One of them must change
Nia:
Yes
Hary:
One must change, so there no pile up
Then, back to stories
Hary:
Stories
Nia:
This?
Hary:
No, that the my profile
the stories Tik
Nia:
Oh the stories, the one with the stories post
Hary:
Stories
Atikah:
This?
Hary:
This is it, in stories there are category
In the category, there an icon
Hary:
There is icon love life, school life, college life, work life,
and many more. There an icon, but it look like inconsistent
Hary:
Look at love life, college life, and work life
Their icon just a line art, just a white line
Hary:
Meanwhile school life, horror, and strangers edition
They use vector so it's not consistent
Hary:
It would be better if use line art then all of them is line art,
all vector then all of them is vector
Hary:
It's not consistent
Nia:
And there a question mark
Atikah:
Yes, that question mark
Nia:
The question mark, I don't understand
Hary:
Yes that, childhood memories with question mark
what? Why not just a picture of child
Nia:
That's right
Atikah:
It's cute
Hary:
It's about childhood right?
If it's riddle question mark, it's clear
Nia:
Yes, maybe just that
Hary:
I think that all
Atikah:
Done?
Hary:
What else? Anyone want to add more?
It's already quite a lot
Hary:
that we must improve
Nia:
Quite a lot
I think it's already done
Hary:
Done?
Nia:
Done maybe?
Maybe, we see it one more time?
Atikah:
How about my bookmark?
Hary:
Oh, right there also features
Dark mode right?
Nia:
Yes, dark mode
This is the dark mode
Hary:
It's quite nice, maybe there some people who had
problem with their eyes. As we can see the background
is all white
Hary:
So, with dark mode features
is more
Hary:
Nice
Atikah:
More refreshing for the eyes
Hary:
More fresh and we can adjust it
this dark mode
Hary:
With some color that good with dark color
Nia:
I think that's all
Hary:
Anything else guys?
Nia:
It's done I think, Atikah? Anything else?
Atikah:
Done
Nia:
Done?
Atikah:
Done
Hary:
Done isn't it?
Nia:
Done I think
Hary:
Oke, then
Okay if it's done, after this we
Hary:
Make the design, after that
We make, before we already know
what should we change
Hary:
We improve, after that we make the design
so this app will be better
Hary:
And then voting, after that
we presentated it to the app developer
Hary:
Okay, if it's done. No more then?
Nia:
I think it's done
Hary:
Okay, if there none
Nia:
I don't know if there more to add, I think none
Hary:
Okay, if there none
Nia:
Maybe, not yet
Hary:
That's right maybe not yet
But, never mind
it's already quite a lot
Hary:
If there anything else, let's just do it at group
If there nothing else
Nia & Atikah:
Okay
Hary:
Thank you Tik
Thank you Ni
Hary:
Sorry
Nia:
Yes, thanks ry
Atikah:
Yes
Hary:
To distrub, no this is our task
Nia:
Yes, our task
Thank you for the time, we can discuss this
Atikah:
Thanks for the time
Hary:
We can make time, in our busy time
so busy time
Nia:
Closing I think?
Hary:
If there nothing else
Yes, if there nothing else. Let's us said Hamdallah,
sincerely says istigfar, and closing prayer
of the assembly
Hary:
Okay, let's close
Wassalamu'alaikum Warahmatullahi Wabarakatuh
Nia & Atikah:
Wa'alaikumsalam Warahmatullahi Wabarakatuh