Bismillah.
Hello, everyone
Good night
Thank you for the time
At this night
*You're welcome*
To see our presentation
Yes
Maybe, let's introduction first
From our team
I am Nia
And Hary?
As for me, my name is Hary Susilo Pratama
You can call me Hary, the nickname
Is a bit different, please don't mind it
Just call me Hary
Continue Tik
My name is Atikah Khonsa
Yes
I think that's all from our team
Maybe there introduction from the others?
Okay, I am Hyudya
Team lead also CEO of Tell
There Yudha Pratama our CFO
There also Natasha our junior developer
And last there Tasha Cornelia
She is our team UI/UX
Wow, so is this complete?
Almost complete
Maybe that's all for the introduction
Maybe we can start the presentation now
Hary? You can start
Okay
Bismillah
May I share screen?
Wait
Done ry
Can you see it?
Yeah it's so dark
I can see it now
Bismillah
Okay, first of all
Before that, this is my design
Before that, this is based on our personal analysis
Maybe our analysis still have mistake and lack many things
We are still in our third semester and we are still newbie
So, we hope if there still many things that lacking or maybe wrong
We hope to get advice and critics from you
And in the end we want to ask for feedback to our design
First, we analysis the first page of Tell
Here, the home page right?
We think
There should be some change
First, in notification
This notification is at right corner
Less visibble to user
Honestly, when I first use it
Like
Oh, there actually notification button
Also merges with the background
Because it's just outline
It's also separated with other button in navigation bottom bar
There also, home here
This is still confusing, because when we click
it's just stay there
Like still, what is it?
Sorry harsh to say, but there no meaning
Right
Yes, useless
Then
There fun corner and stories, with a sentences 'Hi Tellizen'
We are confused
What is fun corner and stories about
We have to serach what the meaning
There no description what fun corner and stories is
and also
I think, there still
An empty space, so
To low, or maybe later
For the latest update, maybe there a new features
That's for home page, then
Second, here
Education is part of fun corner
Fun corner, education
Yes
We see there a plus button
To add post about
Post anything we want confide about education there
That on right corner at the bottom
We think the placement isn't right
Because it's pile up with other features
such as like, reply, and 3 dots
Maybe, we can change it here
Maybe the one hours ago change to right or the others features
So, it didn't pile up like this
Or maybe the plus sign the one who change
That the second one, and then
There more here, on fun corner
the 3 dots above
This is small and quite far above
It's also a bit confusing if we didn't know
it's less visible there
To see my post and my bookmark
It's to far
It's also make us confusing, what is that for
Oh, to see our post and bookmark at fun corner
Then, for stories
In our design, that I make
We have some change
Like stories, my profile, and bookmark here
We put it in front, I will show it later
We also put search in front at home
Also
Continue, on setting
We think there some not suit
The placement of sign out button
If we put sign out up there
We afraid that later user
Will accidently touch the sign out button
because it's up there
Below fingerprint, if they have huge finger
There is a possibility
Usually, sign out put down below everything
We also make some change there
There also in Tellizen community column
This Tellizen community
I think for 'tell on twitter','tell on instagram','tell on medium', or
'tell on discord' like that
Is a repeated words, so
We also make some change there
Also we put user inteface on account
There account, notification, then user interface and later
sign out at the bottom
Like this
As for the design that I make
This is it
Before this, the first page
If we want to open 'Tell'
There a page
Diversion, before we got into 'Tell'
I forgot, at the sign up
'Tell' sign up button is still with white background
plus just google icon and to small, it's unsuitable
Here, we make it with a sentences "sign up with google" with google icon
and we make the color blue
Like this
Click this first, now we are login
This is the view of home page
Like I said before
I said before that my profile, bookmark, and other features
That still separate, now I made it into one
There home, the contents is fun corner and stories
I add some description
I add find to home from my stories
Notification from there to this
Chat features still the same
Profile from my stories I put it here and setting still the same
And then
Before we must went to category
We must went to the category, for example education
Before, here the button is kinda pile up
I change and put it to the left
To add the post
I am not completely remodel design, I still retains the old design
Because I think 'Tell' have their own characteristic on their design
Like this part
What it's called?
The bar on the right
I think this is unique that why I still retains it
If you want to click like this
If you want post, but I also add
So that users are not complicated, that we must went to category
to add post
I add button create a post, so
Just went to fun corner you can add post
But, here I add features category. Why?
So, when they typed
Add the category first
Before they post
Adding just like that
That's what we add on fun corner
Maybe a bit trivial, there is 5 categories. There one on the left
We make it to more right, so it's balanced
And also features search still the same
We make it like this
And for stories still the same, I just add a little here like before
On fun corner
So it can make stories there
Next, notification
I make a little change
Notification like this
Like this
The features still the same, it can send private messages
And also I make some change
Before it's...
Stick
Yes, I make some change
I got inspiration from facebook and others application I use before
Okay
This is chatroom, I polish a little bit
Like this
The chatroom
Done with notification, also chatroom
On going, Pending
And profile, It still the same features
But for draft and bookmark I put it above there
This is for post or stories the user made before
So it will saved there
Before, for fun corner have to be in fun corner
There my post and my bookmark so it's separated
Also in stories there also my stories and my bookmark for stories
But we make into one, so everything on profile
Like this, stories like this
This, I didn't make it. If the bookmark empty
Also the same with draft
My post still the same, the difference is just the background
Users past post, like this
Then now to setting
We make it simple, like this
Here, that was user interface there dark mode and text size
We make into one here
Fingerprint, all of them become one
And what we said before
Tellizen community, it's better to just put the community name
The platform like twitter, instagram, medium, and discord
And the sign out at last
At the bottom, not make users confused
There also dark mode features
Like this
Same with contact us via email, term condition, privacy policy, and attribution
I make it a bit light
It's not quite visible on light mode
On my personal opinion, there not many people who want to know about that
Okay, if we sign out
We go back to the first page, like this
Okay that's all
Our analysis
Maybe back to MC?
To Nia
Maybe that's all for our team design presentation
Maybe we may know how the feedback is?
From our design
How the feedback
Okay, guys I am gonna give the feedback first
Overall I appreaciate, this is great honestly I appreaciate it
This is cool from 3rd semester student, I already saw some of the design
Just from that is already enough, not enough but just right
Know how to place it, even from the UI and UX
But I don't want to say much from UI/UX
Later for Miss Cornel to said it
First, I want to tell you about the first button here
The sign in
From a technical point of view
We use library from google, so for customized is takes a lot times
So, sometimes there developer who just went 'just like that'
And customize from google is hard
That the feedback I can give to you guys, so you guys know
There some developer not that they don't want to, but because it's hard
to customized
And then
The last one in the setting
I actually disagree when you said, people didn't care about contact us via email
The truth is we are
I meant we are community base, so user will try reach us to developer directly
Even via instagram, twitter, or discord. Because
Some want to contact via email, why to email
Because, first by email is the privacy and really two-way direction
And really know who it is in social media
They talk more, usually there complaint about banned
(Example)
And that was quite long, not something to do at twitter or instagram
that why it's should went to email
And whe you said it's not concern, that actually a concern for
privacy policy and term condition
Why like that? because if we talk about community base
Tell is anonymous right?
Because of that, there some users
Insecure, was the developer
Get any my information, but what?
That why we make it visible, so
So if they want to se our privacy policy about what we do with the information
You can see it, it meant as written, and visible also get clicked
That's why we make it bold so it can be seen
same with term and condition, because
There still many thing that get questioned in the community
What I can and can't do here, that's why there is term and condition
like I can't curse here or say anything sexual
We make it visible, so there no one who gonna say that I didn't see it
So, we close the chance for users to say
that they didn't see or don't know about it
That's from the community side
Honestly we, from me personally I appreciate it so much because
Why?
So, honestly why we harshly speaking have a messy design
And I admit it, it's very messy
Because we are still test
What we test is not the UI but the function
Tell founded in 2018
We tried if Tell like this what gonna happen
The released new version with UI like this what gonna happen
Change again to version 3, the one you guys use
And that's why we are doing this questioner in this month is for
The version 4 will be better on UI/UX and neat
That's all from my view
Actually I want to talk about button, but I will let Mr. Yudha or
Miss Cornel about that
I think that's all
Thank you
If you see, from UI/UX side
There is color contrast
Have you heard it before?
As for me not yet
So, color contrast is
About how sentences and background can't be unseen
So it should nice to look at
Okay next
I want to ask, why the google icon is on the right not the left
It's from how we pronounce, so sign up with and there the google icon
Okay, but it would be better if there an icon like that
Icon on the left and sign up with google still written
Still write the google?
Yes
Okay next, anything else?
Visual hierarchy, have you heard visual hierarchy before?
Visual hierarchy, it's like position? Where the eye is first fixed on
Yes
You want to highlight fun corner and stories
It's better if the color isn't the same with the detail/description
The difference can't small, the font size
Size in button small normal large
This
Yes
There also a minimal for the height, that is 32
Okay
Okay, as from me
Overall good from the design
Quite fresh for us
There many inspiration we got for reference
Some feedback from me is
The placement for the button
We make it the design like that, there is some consideration in it
First for example
This plus button, to add post
We put it on the right, just because it's easy to reach
With thumb
I think on setting
My feedback is same with the others, actually this is good
The account become one
The config above and Tellizen is a good input, we can consider it
I think that's all from me, what else?
Thank you
You're welcome
Maybe that's all?
That's all from us
Anything else?
Maybe more?
Overall, there not really. Honestly from me we appreciate it
This is cool, we have
We need input because we are going for Tell 4v
There so much more
Thing we need to fix, also reference from you guys is also a happy thing
Done?
Yes it's
Thank you so much to Tell Developer team
To make time for us
We are sorry, because our design is still far from perfect
Still need to get fixed
It's okay everyone start from zero, we are all still learning
We also happy, also appreciate to meet Tell Developer team, to have the chance
to redesign and get the feedback from the developer directly
That's right
That's right ry
Thank you for Tell Developer team to give feedback to our design
We are sorry if our design analysis is still deviated
Thank you, Should I close it?
Yes
It's okay
Okay, Assalamu'alaikum
Good Night
Wa'alaikumsalam